<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepages on Evangeline Corridor Forward</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepages on Evangeline Corridor Forward</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/homepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plan Recommendations</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/1_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/1_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>A Shared Vision for Economic Revitalization The Economic Action Plan builds on a year-long process of targeted stakeholder and community engagement, economic and technical research, and urban design and planning, integrating multiple past plans and ongoing investments to develop a comprehensive strategy for economic development along the proposed I-49 Connector project in Lafayette, LA.​&#xA;​For neighborhoods along the Evangeline Corridor—the 3 miles adjacent to the I-49 Connector—the proposed infrastructural upgrade offers significant opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/2_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/2_process/</guid>
      <description>Process The planning process commenced in November 2023 and will concluded during the fall of 2024. It consisted of several interrelated work streams as follows: Identify opportunities: The project team analyzed a wide range of data related to existing conditions, engaged the community and stakeholders, and developed a list of project recommendations. Measure economic impact: The team conducted analysis to quantify and specify indicators related to economic growth and equitable development for the recommended projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goals</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/3_goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/3_goals/</guid>
      <description>Goals Five core goals were identived for the Economic Action Plan vetted through stakeholderand community engagement. These goals aim to build a thriving, equitable community through economic opportunities, quality housing, social resilience, local capacity, and strategic investments.&#xA;####Goal 1: Enhance Access to Economic Opportunities Provide quality jobs and career pathways Expand and retain businesses Capture unique market trends and opportunities Support entrepreneurs and small enterprises Ensure both local opportunities and broader benefits ####Goal 2: Ensure Quality Housing &amp;amp; Neighborhood Amenities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Input</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/4_public_input/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/4_public_input/</guid>
      <description>Engaging the Community and Stakeholders: The project team conducted a series of engagement activities to understand the community&amp;rsquo;s vision, incorporate input from local stakeholders and experts, and review draft recommendations. The process includes the following types of engagement:&#xA;Stakeholder focus groups: In December 2023, the team met with 25 participants representing the Housing Development community, the Business community, Community Stakeholders for History, Culture, Recreation &amp;amp; Education, and Faith Group &amp;amp; Residents.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/5_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/5_events/</guid>
      <description>Upcomming Public Open House A concluding open house is being scheduled during September of 2024 to provide an opportunity for the project team to deliver a summary presentation describing the Evangeline Corridor Economic Action Plan, to discuss ideas and exhibits face-to-face, and to receive a final round of public input. The plan will have been through preliminary review by Lafayette Consolidated Government (LCG) and the Evangeline Thruway Redevelopment Team (ETRT) among others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partners</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/6_partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/6_partners/</guid>
      <description>Partners This is a bold plan to remediate long-term disinvestment along the Evangeline Thruway corridor. It will require a broad and diverse coalition of public, private and non-profit entities working collaboratively as partners with a shared vision.&#xA;To date, ​Partners include&amp;hellip; the Lafayette Public Trust Financing Authority (LPTFA) and Lafayette Economic Development Authority (LEDA).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acknowledgements</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/homepage/7_acknowledgements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/homepage/7_acknowledgements/</guid>
      <description>The Economic Action Plan was commissioned by the Lafayette Consolidated Government (LCG) and the Evangeline Thruway Redevelopment Team (ETRT) in partnership with the Lafayette Public Trust Financing Authority (LPTFA) and Lafayette Economic Development Authority (LEDA).&#xA;The Economic Action Plan was produced by a multidisciplinary Consultant Team led by James Lima Planning + Development (JLP+D). Members of the Consultant Team include AQ Studios, Partnership for Southern Equity, Franklin Associates, Lafayette Habitat for Humanity, and HDR.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
